<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Safeguide 1</string>
    <string name="open">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="safeguide">SafeGuide</string>
    <string name="start">START</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="greeting_message_description">Greeting message for the user</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="tsk">ggg</string>

    <string name="view_evacuation_map">View evacuation map</string>
    <string name="Paragraph_1">This is a gentle reminder that, while our emergency preparedness application is a useful tool for users, it is crucial to understand its purpose properly. Our software is intended to assist users in navigating before, during, and after a disaster, providing vital guidelines and resources for safety and recovery.</string>
    <string name="Paragraph_2">However, it is important to understand that the application alone cannot save lives. Instead, it provides users with information and direction to help them make informed decisions and take appropriate action in times of crisis.</string>
    <string name="Paragraph_3">Remember, preparation is essential. Stay informed, plan  ahead, and utilize our app as a resource to help you prepare for any emergency.</string>

 ced
    <string name="about_us_paragraph1"> Safeguide is designed to ensure the safety and preparedness of students, faculty, staff, and visitors at Cavite State University - Cavite City Campus. Our mission is to provide timely information, practical resources, and essential tools to help our campus community effectively prepare for and respond to various types of disasters.</string>
    <string name="about_us_paragraph3"> For more information or support, please reach out to our Safeguide team at app.safeguide@gmail.com or visit our office at the Department of Information and Technology.</string>
    <string name="about_us_paragraph2"> Safeguide is specifically developed with the needs of Cavite State University - Cavite City Campus in mind. Our localized approach ensures that all information and resources are relevant and actionable for our community. By leveraging technology, Safeguide aims to build a culture of preparedness and resilience, empowering each individual to act effectively in the face of disaster.</string>



    <string-array name="itemTexts">
 main
        <item>Item 1</item>
        <item>Item 2</item>
        <item>Item 3</item>
        <item>Item 4</item>
        <item>Item 5</item>
        <item>Item 6</item>
        <item>Item 7</item>
        <item>Item 8</item>
        <item>Item 9</item>
        <item>Item 10</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="itemTexts2">
        <item>Item 1</item>
        <item>Item 2</item>
        <item>Item 3</item>
        <item>Item 4</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="itemTexts3">
        <item>Item 1</item>
        <item>Item 2</item>
        <item>Item 3</item>
        <item>Item 4</item>
        <item>Item 5</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="itemTexts4">
        <item>Item 1</item>
        <item>Item 2</item>
        <item>Item 3</item>
        <item>Item 4</item>
        <item>Item 5</item>
        <item>Item 6</item>
        <item>Item 7</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="itemTexts5">
        <item>Item 1</item>
        <item>Item 2</item>
        <item>Item 3</item>
        <item>Item 4</item>
        <item>Item 5</item>
        <item>Item 6</item>
        <item>Item 7</item>
        <item>Item 8</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>